<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>wow is the future!</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on wow is the future!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced</title>
      <link>http://example.org/advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/advanced/</guid>
      <description>Getting the CLI Wallet LINUX Download the Linux 64-bit command line client and extract it
wget https://downloads.getwownero.org/linux64 tar jxvf linux64 MAC Download the Mac command line client and extract it
wget https://downloads.getwownero.org/mac64 tar jxvf mac64 WINDOWS Create a new folder with Windows File Explorer, and use your web browser to download the following file to the new folder https://downloads.getwownero.org/win64
Double click the Wownero zip file that has been downloaded to extract it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downloads</title>
      <link>http://example.org/downloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/downloads/</guid>
      <description>Get wowlite Graphical Interface Linux GUI Wowlite Linux v0.8
Mac OS GUI Wowlite macOS v0.8
Windows GUI Wowlite Windows v0.8
Get wownero Command Line Interface (The CLI wallet is for Advanced Users)
Linux CLI Wow-cli Linux v0.8
Mac OS CLI Wow-cli macOS v0.8
Windows CLI Wow-cli Windows v0.8</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start</title>
      <link>http://example.org/quickstart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/quickstart/</guid>
      <description>Getting wowlite Click downloads at the top of the page and choose the version for your operating system (macOS, Windows, or Linux). Once downloaded use Unzip to extract the wallet file. You should be left with a folder called wowlite-(version), open that folder. On MacOS you will install the dmg.
 Running wowlite MacOS Wowlite should now be in your available applications, add to launcher for convienence.
Linux Look for wowlite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trade</title>
      <link>http://example.org/trade/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/trade/</guid>
      <description>TradeOgre</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://example.org/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/intro/</guid>
      <description>What is Wow? Wownero is a CPU-mineable memecoin. It is a software fork of Monero with a lite version of RandomX (1MB scratchpad), a ring size of 22, and a faster difficulty adjustment.
Wownero has a deflationary finite supply of 184,467,440 coins with a slow and steady emission over 50 years.
Wownero is a fairly launched coin with no premine, instamine, or dev tax.
 WTF does that mean? How Wownero can help you?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>